<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<anything>
    Alcohol
    <alcohol>Moet</alcohol>
    References to: brands of alcohol, consumption of alcohol, drinking games, effects of alcohol, and colloquial terms for types of alcohol.
    
    
    Criticism
    <criticism>Slipping like fishes, choking when you hit the cypher</criticism>
    Criticism of the rap game and of phony rappers.
    
    
    Drugs
    <drugs>the crack,
        they overdose</drugs>
    References to: hard drugs, use and sale of hard drugs, and users of hard drugs.
    
    
    Fashion
    <fashion>lo, like Ralph</fashion>
    References to fashion designers and brands, as well as references to articles of clothing.
    
    
    Food
    <food>kiwi</food>
    Any mention of food, in any form. Also, mentions of consumption of food.
    
    
    Geographical Locations
    <geo ref="Brooklyn">Brooklyn</geo>
    All references to geographical locations, whether explicit or implicit.
    
    
    Guns
    <guns>the heater</guns>
    References to guns, both direct and indirect.
    
    
    Haters
    <haters>Closed-minded men</haters>
    This tag denotes those who do not enjoy Joey's music or who do not support him. Also refers to those who are only interested in being around Joey due to his fame and fortune.
    
    
    Hip Hop
    The hip hop tag always refers to a rapper or rap group, but these references occur in several ways:
    directly referencing a song or artist name (this example refers to a song by rapper Rick Ross entitled BMF: Blowing Money Fast);
    <hiphop ref="RickRoss">BMF like Ross
        man</hiphop>
    indirectly referencing a figure in hip hop using symbolism and figurative language (this example refers to Joey's hip hop collective Pro Era, which has 47 closeknit members);
    <hiphop ref="ProEra">47 friends in my circumference</hiphop>
    and references to figures in hip hop by quoting or paraphrasing another rapper's raps (this example shows Joey rapping lyrics from Jay-Z's Song Cry).
    <hiphop ref="Jay-Z">I couldn't see it coming down <group label="e" num="1" rhyme="2 3">my</group>
        <group label="e" num="2" rhyme="1 3">eye</group>
    </hiphop>
    <hiphop ref="Jay-Z">So I had to make the song <group label="e" num="3" rhyme="1 2">cry</group>
    </hiphop>
    
    
    History
    <history>Underground Railroad</history>
    This tag denotes a reference to a historical event or figure (including figures in ancient mythology).
    
    
    Money
    This tag is used to mark any references to money, divided into two qualifications, pursuit of money and possession of money.
     example of pursuit of money:
    <money qual="pursuit">plotting on that <group label="c" num="6" slantRhyme="5">dime</group>
    </money>
     example of possession of money:
    <money qual="possession">pockets <AAVE field="syn" type="deletion" class="copula"/>healthy
        <group label="b" num="19" rhyme="18">green</group>
    </money>
    
    
    Oldschool
    <oldschool>back in the days</oldschool>
    This tag indicates a reference or phrase indicating that Joey is talking about things that invoke nostalgia and hearken back to past times.
    
    
    Pop Culture
    <popculture ref="Twitter">
        <group label="c" num="14" rhyme="15">Twitter</group>
    </popculture>
    <popculture ref="JackSparrow">jack the booty like I'm Sparrow</popculture>
    
    
    Power
    <power>Jakes</power>
    <power>Jim Crow Laws</power>
    
    
    Religion
    The religion tag here is reflective of the spiritual beliefs found in the lyrics of our corpus. In some cases this refers to Christian ideas, 
    while in other cases this tag marks references to third eye spiritualism.
    <religion>God bless the heaven</religion>
    <religion>on some third eye shit</religion>
    
    
    Sex
    This tag marks all sexual acts, tacit and implicit. 
    This example, bacchanalian, is a word for 'drunken orgy' that comes from an ancient Greek festival celebrating Bacchus, god of wine.
    <sex>
        <alcohol>bacchanalian</alcohol>
    </sex>
    
    
    Sports
    This tag marks all sports references. These can refer to an athlete or sports figure and also to general sports-related terms and objects.
    <sports>Al <group label="d" num="10" assimilation="8 9">Pujols</group></sports>
    <sports>hoops</sports>
    
    
    Struggle
    The purpose of this tag is to indicate any raps that talk about the difficulties of life at various stages of life and wealth.
    <struggle>And I'm from the blocks where they sell</struggle>
   
    
    Success
    This tag indicates either Joey's pursuit of or possession of success. This comes in a variety of colorful expressions that are all quite varied.
     an example of possession of success is the boast:
    <success qual="possession">I'm killin' this shit</success>
     while an example of pursuit of success is the statement that Joey will continue to work hard until he gets to the point where he is famous enough to be on Jay-Z's radar,
     and wealthy enough to afford to purchase a Range Rover for his mother.
    <success qual="pursuit">Won't stop 'til I meet <group label="h" num="2" slantRhyme="1">
            <hiphop ref="Jay-Z">Hova</hiphop>
        </group> and my <women qual="pos">momma's</women> in a <group label="h" num="3"
            rhyme="1 4 5">
            <popculture ref="RangeRover">Rover</popculture>
        </group>
    </success>
    
    
    Violence
    <violence>Rip your lips off your <group label="e" num="15" slantRhyme="14">mouth</group>
    </violence>
    The violence tag is used to denote any indication of violent behavior, both from Joey and his people and simply generally in the hood.
    
    
    Weed
    <weed>exotic piff</weed>
    This tag is used to mark any instance where Joey discusses marijuana-related activities.
    
    
    Women
    This tag marks references to women, and is divided into two groups using qualifiers positive and negative, which label the connotation of the marked word or phrase.
     an example of women negative:
     -bitch-
     an example of women positive:
     -my momma-
</anything>
